hi guys today I'll be showing you the
best way to get the perfect French money
on natural nails using dip powder I have
a few tricks that will help you get a
clean smile line every time and a little
gadget that's going to make it so much
easier let me go ahead and show you how
I do it
[Music]
okay loves we're gonna start off by
prepping the nail I'm going to drill the
shine off her nail bed and making sure I
get the sides and as close to the
cuticle as possible to avoid lifting I'm
then going to dehydrate and prime the
nail using bond I'm going in with my
base and applying it to the top
three-quarters of the nail make sure
your brush is flat like so and apply
enough base to create an even layer this
will create an apex so don't apply base
to the nail walls just yet it's now time
to dip so I'm going to grab my desired
pink shade and instead of pushing the
finger into the jar I'm going to bring
the jar to the nail until it is fully
covered use a fluffy brush to clean off
the remaining powder and maintain a
clean surface and as you guys can see
our nail is now ready for French Dip
application now the key to getting a
perfect smile line is in this little
gadget the Kira Skye French case is
designed to make it extremely easy to
create the perfect French set every time
I'm gonna prep my workspace so I'm
grabbing my pure white and pouring a
generous amount into the case I'm then
going to shake it lightly to create an
even surface for dipping apply base a
hairline away from the cuticle and this
is where you want to go in and cover the
sidewalls remember to keep your brush
flat for even application I'm now gonna
grab my French case and dip the finger
in at a 45-degree angle until I get the
desired smile line hold the finger
steady and pull straight out now hold
the finger down and tap off the excess
for the pink powder on the rest of the
nail you don't want to dip into the pink
because this could cause the colors to
bleed together so pouring is the key to
a crisp line remember to tap and lightly
brush off the excess every time that you
dip I'm going to apply base to the
entire nail again and dip one more time
into the French case making sure to
align it to the previous smile line
again we want to hold the finger down
when tapping off x-4 your pink on top
one more time and dust off any excess
once I'm done dipping into the white and
pink we can go in with our seal fur
tight I'm going to apply a generous coat
and wait a few minutes for it to dry
once it is dry we can go in to file and
shape the nail you can go in with an e
file to cut down on time but if you
follow the proper steps when applying
your base then you shouldn't really need
to file that much buff the nail to
create a smooth surface and dust off any
excess powder with a fluffy brush
[Music]
apply a second layer of seal protect and
allow it to dry for about a minute or so
or until you complete your other four
fingers I'm now going to rub the seal
protect into the nail by using a lint
free wipe we're going to finish this
look off by applying a thin even layer
of topcoat without overlapping allow
this to dry and apply a second layer to
the nail this second layer is what's
going to add shine you don't want to
wait too long between your seconds so
you'll protect application and your
first topcoat so I would recommend doing
one hand at a time to make sure your
glazes are drying properly always make
sure to finish your mani by applying
cuticle oil and rubbing upward and
here's our final look as you guys can
see we have a perfect smile line and
there was no sculpting or sand so needed
thank you so much for watching if you
like this video don't forget to
subscribe to be notified when we post
again and if you would like to purchase
your own Cara Skye French starter kit
click on the link below I'll see you
guys in the next video bye
[Music]